foreclosureindia.com 2016-06-28

# Bank Property Auctions India, Legal Services, Privacy policy- Foreclosure India

This privacy policy describes how we handle your personal information. We collect, use, and share personal information to help the 4Closure website (ForeclosureIndia.com) work and to keep it safe.

All information posted in ForeclosureIndia.com is publicly available.However we are presenting it over the Internet media so at to make easier to get.

Any information which we collect of the users via registration such as e-mail ID, Ph.Number etc and while browsing such as IP address will be stored on our servers and our local systems located in our office in Hyderabad.(Browsing data is collected by cookies,If you don't want this data to be collected cookies can be disabled )

All information which we collected will be used by us to notify you of updates(Can be disabled by notifying us info@foreclosureindia.com),get your feedback,troubleshoot problems and calculate our site statistics such as avg.time spent on site,no of page views etc... so that we can find out where we are lacking and improve the site.

The users privacy is very important to us. We do not and shall not at any point in time, either sell or rent users personal information to third parties without users explicit consent. 

We may be required from time to time to disclose users personal information to Governmental or law enforcing agencies or our regulators, but we will only do so under proper authority.

We may also disclose personal information to enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other's rights, or protects anyone's rights, property or safety.

We may also share personal information with:  

  * Corporate affiliates who help detect or prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to). 
  * Service providers who help with our business operations.

You may use personal information gathered from ForeclosureIndia.com only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam/ phising or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that.

We use third party advertisements on our site to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Mumbai real estate ads to someone in Mumbai, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). You can view their privacy policy by clicking here.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We use a number of mechanisms (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect the security and integrity of your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. So while we strive to protect such information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once any personal information comes into our possession, we will take reasonable steps to protect that information from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

Users who use any of the features on ForeclosureIndia.com agree and accept that they have been fully informed by ForeclosureIndia.com that the use of features may lead to publication of any personal information posted by them while using any specific feature on ForeclosureIndia.com. Users further agree that the authenticity of, and consequences from the posting by users of any personal information of themselves or any other person, are the sole responsibility of the user. Users further agree and accept that the terms of the Privacy Policy will be applicable to the use of all features, existing and new. However, the Users agree and accept that confidentiality of information posted on such features has been waived by the Users of such features themselves.

We may update, upgrade, modify (partially &/or fully) this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next visit or after 7 days, whichever is sooner. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply. Send questions about this policy to support@foreclosureindia.com
